What's the result ?
Amazing !
Amazing, isn't it ?
Hello, I'm Haruka Kaki
I'm Nagi Inoue
I'm Urumi Morihira
We are now...
Ta-da !
We are at the Anabuki Arena in Kagawa
So, today, of course
Nogizaka46 Summer All-Japan Tour 2025
PR Operation in Kagawa
It's too hot !
It's super sunny !
Today, we are in such a hot country
While we are doing the PR for the national tour
We are going to tell you the good points of Kagawa
We are doing it all over the country
This is the last place
I'm looking forward to it
Is it your first time to come to Kagawa ?
Yes, it's my first time
Hello !
Nice to meet you
So cute !
Nogizaka fans
On this tour
You may be the first one to come
We are going to stand in the same line of sight as them
Today, the three of us are going to know the charm of Kagawa
Let's go !
Today, we are going to go inside
Excuse me
It smells like a new building
It was only built in February this year
That's right
It's so beautiful !
Amazing !
The seats are colorful
What should I do ?
Like this ?
So cute !
It's so spacious !
It's spacious !
I don't feel it all the time
But when there is no one around, my voice echoes
It echoes
Can you make a loud voice ?
Say Kagawa
Sure
Kagawa !
It echoes a lot !
Amazing !
It's beautiful !
The distance is close
It's close
When the stage is done, it feels closer
That's right
Haruka, you go down
Go down to the stage
Let's go !
There she is !
I can hear her voice !
I'm so happy !
Find Nagi and Urumi
Find them
Where are they ?
The correct answer is
Here !
It echoes !
So cute !
I can tell
Amazing !
What did they dance ?
Manatsubiyo !
Correct !
Amazing !
Can you put a PR poster on the stage ?
Let's go together
Sure
Excuse me
Nagizaka46 is going to perform here
Can you put a poster on the stage ?
Of course
Thank you
They are so strong !
We did it !
Here we are !
Here we are at Kitahama alley
Shall we go further ?
Very cute !
This is cute !
This red light is cute
It's fashionable
Fashionable
What we are going to do now is
a fashion magazine
Oh, a magazine
A magazine
We can feel the Kagao
I'm looking forward to it
Isn't it here ?
Oh, here !
Kitahama
Oh, that's right
Blue stories
Kitahama blue stories
Here we are
Oh, it's cool
It's cute
Excuse me
It's a nice shop with a calm atmosphere
Oh, wings
It's cute
It's fashionable
Ta-da !
It's like we are on a date
It's cute
I'm 166 cm
I look at the same height
like this
I look at Urumi from here
It's 166 cm
Yes, it's 166 cm
And
Oh, Nagi
I'm about the same height as Urumi
I'm small
So cute !
I want to draw a pattern
I want to draw it
It's a blue button of happiness
What ?
Do you want to be happy ?
I want to be happy
Then, let's choose what we like
Wow !
Here
There are three blue buttons
Which one ?
Which one should we choose ?
Let's point our fingers
Okay
One, two, three
Oh, I got it
This one
Really ?
Yes
Then, this one
I'm happy
Look at it directly
It's cute
Let's buy it together
Yes
Blue button
I want to be happy
Thank you
Could you put the poster of PR on this store ?
It's okay
Thank you
Okay
We went shopping
Thank you
It seems that the next place is nearby
Let's walk there
Okay
We arrived
Ta-da! Element
It says 88
Wow
We found 88
It's retro
It's nice
It's an original T-shirt
There are many kinds
It's true
It's cute
Udon, 88
There are 88
It's the same number
It's perfect
Yes
It's perfect for this summer
This summer
There are many games
Wow
It's very retro
Look
Which hand has an apple in it ?
It says Goritan
It's funny
Goritan
It's 100 yen
It's true
Let's try it
I want to try it
Let's go
Hello
You can compete against Doshan Gorita
What is it ?
Press the button
It means luck ?
It means luck
Press the button
It's crying
Then
Which one ?
Right
Yes
What ?
You can't eat it
I see
Let's do it again
Can we do it again ?
Wait a minute
Does it mean it's different from the previous one ?
It's true
I don't think I can do it twice
I don't think I can do it
Can you press the button ?
It's not different from the previous one
Have you seen that dog ?
Really ?
The dog's mouth
Seems that a ball can get in it
Let's play a nostalgic game
Let's do it
Let's go
Yes
It's a snack
It's a dog
Wait a minute
It's delicious
Where is it ?
I wanted to eat it
I'm sorry
It's a snack
Let's do it again
Thank you
It's difficult
What is this ?
Wait a minute
It doesn't fit
It's gone
It's difficult
What is this ?
I don't understand the theory
But it comes out
It comes out
It was interesting
Yes, it was interesting
Hanged!
Hanged to the entrance
This is Ichiba Aquarium
It says Yashima Aquarium under Ichiba Aquarium
New Yashima Aquarium is being renovated
The fish and the animals living in the sea are displayed here
10 minutes by car from Anabuki Arena
If you work hard, you can walk 30 minutes
It's a little hot
I hope only those who can do water supply can walk
If you can do it, I think the car will be happy
Let's go
I'm happy
I like the aquarium
It's a jellyfish
Jellyfish
It's amazing
It's good
It's cute
It's nice
Look
It's cute
What is it ?
I'm curious
It's space
It's cute
If you drop the food in the hole, it will come out
I'll give it to you in order
Please
I'll give it to you
It's cute
I got it
Thank you
It's cute
It's here
Look
I got it
Thank you
It's amazing
You can do it with your hands
It's cute
Thank you
I'm hungry
It's cute
It's a penguin
Penguin
It's close
I can see it from here
It's very close
I've never seen it from here
It's like a meet and greet
Meet and greet
It's like a space
Hello
I came from Tokyo
It's gone
It's a penguin
It's coming
It's walking
Why don't you come ?
I can't go back
It's cute how it walks
It's cute
It walks like Aya
It's Aya
Do you want to try it ?
Kawausokuji
You can't miss it
It's very attractive
I wonder if I can get it
I got it
It's on
Here I go
One, two
Nito
It's big
Kawausokuji
I got Nito's Kawausokuji
It's cute
Haruka-san is holding Kawausokuji
I got it
It's a small Kawausokuji
It's small
It's cute
It's three
I'm happy
I got it
It's time to eat
Let's go to eat delicious foods in Kagawa
I was waiting for it!
Let's go
I'm starving
We're so
Look like that
Maybe people sometimes say that they are Kawauso face
That's true
I thought about it
When I met this girl
I thought she looked like her
You are right
That's true
Cute
Urutaro
Got it
This girl is Urutaro
Urumin and Urutaro
Cute
She's a boy
You look like a grown-up
I look like a grown-up
Let's go together
Yes, let's go
We're here
Ikkaku-san
We're going to eat lunch
Yes
Kagawa is famous for udon
I think everyone eats udon
It's different
Chicken?
Big chicken
Chicken with bones
I want to eat chicken with bones
I'm looking forward to it for the first time
It looks delicious
It's a little spicy
It's true
Chicken with bones
70 years
Wow
Please enjoy the taste of the specialty store
There are chicken with bones and chicken with bones
There is
I want to eat chicken with bones today
I want to eat
3 chicken with bones
Thank you
Is there any recommended way to eat?
That's right
With the sauce of the chicken
It is recommended to eat with a knot
What is a knot?
Onigiri
Mutsubi
Is there any recommended way to eat?
3 people
Thank you
Mutsubi is cool
I'm going to say it from now on
Mutsubi
What do you eat for breakfast?
Cool
That's right
It seems to be completely different from Tebasaki-tama in Nagoya
It's big
It looks pretty big
I'm looking forward to it
I wonder how big it is
It may be
It's about this
I expect
I expect that
It's a little brown
I'm scared
Thank you
3 minutes
How far should I go?
Thank you
Is it heavy?
Amazing
It's good because the oil is dripping
This is a very good color
It's baked
It looks delicious
Let's eat
I have to be careful not to spill it
It sounds good
Wow
Amazing
Is it amazing?
It's crispy
It's very juicy
It's very soft
Try it
I'll eat
Is it good?
Amazing
It's crispy
The spiciness comes later
Right after eating
It's like chicken
Chicken
It's getting spicier
Can I try it?
Thank you
Wow
Is it good?
Amazing
It's delicious
I'm scared
It's amazing
It's very soft
The pepper
The smell is amazing
I know
It's crispy
I want to eat more
It's delicious
Let's eat it
It's cute
It's very cute
Wow
This
Amazing
It's delicious
The spiciness comes later
Right
I'll eat it
Doesn't it come later?
It's coming
I want to eat it again
It's true
It's more refreshing than I thought
I can eat it quickly
I know
Can I break it?
You can't
I want to eat it quickly
That's good
I'll eat it
Amazing
It's delicious
When I eat it separately
It's full of fat
It's good
It's delicious
I didn't know there was such a delicious food
I didn't know
If I had known earlier, my life would have changed
You regret it a lot
Can I put on the real poster?
It's okay
Thank you
I'm happy
Today's plan is over
It's over
It was so fast
It was so fun
It was fun
I was able to go to various places
All the places are close to the arena
Everyone
Everyone is going to play
I hope you can go
I'm full
I feel good
I'm happy
We are also
I will do my best in Kagawa
I will do my best
Bye
Thank you for your viewing